http://cowartinsurance.com/privacy-policy

Skip to content
770-339-0447 1000 Hurricane Shoals Rd NE Suite B-600Lawrenceville, Georgia 30043 Toggle navigation
HomeInsuranceClaims & ServiceBlogAboutContactPrivacy Policy Cowart Insurance AgencyYour privacy is very important to us. Accordingly, we have developed this Policy in order for you to understand how we collect, use, communicate and disclose and make use of personal information. The following outlines our privacy policy.Before or at the time of collecting personal information, we will identify the purposes for which information is being collected.We will collect and use of personal information solely with the objective of fulfilling those purposes specified by us and for other compatible purposes, unless we obtain the consent of the individual concerned or as required by law.We will only retain personal information as long as necessary for the fulfillment of those purposes.We will collect personal information by lawful and fair means and, where appropriate, with the knowledge or consent of the individual concerned.Personal data should be relevant to the purposes for which it is to be used, and, to the extent necessary for those purposes, should be accurate, complete, and up-to-date.We will protect personal information by reasonable security safeguards against loss or theft, as well as unauthorized access, disclosure, copying, use or modification.We will make readily available to customers information about our policies and practices relating to the management of personal information.We are committed to conducting our business in accordance with these principles in order to ensure that the confidentiality of personal information is protected and maintained. Get a QuoteGive us some info and we'll get quotes from multiple companies.Get a Quote
Toggle Dropdown AutoHomeownerLifeMotorcycleBusinessMore…Insurance Partners
From Our Blog Don’t Delay — Start Thinking About Winterizing Your RV Today December 10, 2020
Commercial Policy Audits Explained November 30, 2020
What is water backup coverage and why is it important? November 16, 2020
Connect OnlineAbout Us Cowart Insurance Agency is an independent insurance agency located in Lawrenceville, Georgia. Cowart Insurance Agency Provides Car, Home, Business, Life, Annuities and Long Term Care Insurance to All of Georgia, Including Lawrenceville, Suwanee, Buford, Sugar Hill, Dacula, Hoschton, Braselton, Flowery Branch, Jefferson, and Winder.HomeAboutContactSitemapRecent Articles Don’t Delay — Start Thinking About Winterizing Your RV Today
Commercial Policy Audits Explained
What is water backup coverage and why is it important? Quick LinksAbout UsContact UsService CenterInsurance ProductsGet an Insurance QuoteCompanies We RepresentStaff DirectoryContact Us 1000 Hurricane Shoals Rd NE Suite B-600Lawrenceville, Georgia 30043 770-339-0447 770-936-1930 email [at] cowartinsurance [dot] com email [at] cowartinsurance [dot] com Mon-Fri 9am-5pm © 2020 Cowart Insurance Agency | Search | Privacy | Disclaimer
